You'd rather push him,
encourage him, adjure him,
encourage him,
command him to do what is
right.
You'd rather push him,
encourage him, to do what is
right,
if you don't do all these
things.
The other alternative that
you have is
that
La yadribanna Allahu bi kulu
bi ba'dhikum
ala ba'dh.
Oh la yadribanna Allahu bi
kulu bi
ba'dhikum ala ba'dh.
The alternative you have is
that
Yadribanna Allahu bi kulu bi
ba'dhikum ala
ba'dh.
Allah will set the hearts of
some
of you against the others.
If you don't make al-amru bil
ma'ruf,
if you don't make al-nahyuan
al-munkar,
if you don't hold back the
hand
of the Musi,
wa la ta'akhu dhunna ala
yadil Musi,
oh that, wa la ta'aturunna hu
ala
al-Haqqi apra,
oh that you necessarily push
him and
encourage him towards Haqq,
if you don't do these things.
La yadribanna Allahu bi kulu
bi ba'dhikum
ala ba'dh.
Oh you Muslims, Allah will
turn the
hearts of some of you against
the
others.